{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q1",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q1.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q1.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q1.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q1.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q1.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q2",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q2.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q2.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q2.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q2.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q2.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q3",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q3.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q3.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q3.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q3.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q3.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q4",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q4.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q4.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q4.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q4.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q4.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q5",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q5.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q5.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q5.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q5.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q5.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q6",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q6.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q6.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q6.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q6.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q6.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q7",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q7.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q7.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q7.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q7.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q7.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q8",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q8.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q8.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q8.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q8.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q8.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q9",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q9.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q9.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q9.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q9.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q9.opt1"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz.circuit.q10",
      "options": [
        "quiz.circuit.q10.opt1",
        "quiz.circuit.q10.opt2",
        "quiz.circuit.q10.opt3",
        "quiz.circuit.q10.opt4"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "quiz.circuit.q10.opt1"
    }
  ]
}